Guide to the Southern Poverty Law Center Intelligence Project Collection, 1940s-2020; 1940s-ongoing RL.10135
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Documented Organizations, 1940s-2000s; 1
  - Gospel of Christ Kingdom Church-National Chaplain's Association, 140
    - Literature, 1991 (Box 3)
      Proclaim Liberty newsletter inserts, other materials.
    - Catalogs, 1992 (Box 3)
      Christian Law Journal catalogs.
    - Catalogs, 1992 (Box 3)
      Soldiers of the Cross catalogs and subscription forms. Also includes "Tenants of the Faith" pamphlet.
    - Literature, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
      Weapons of W.A.R. newsletter excerpts.
    - Literature, undated (Box 3)
      Miscellaneous literature excerpts.
  - Guderian Books, 141
    - Catalogs, 1999-2001 (Box 3)
      Milton
  - Gun List, 142
    - Mass mailing, 1998 (Box 3)
      Gun Show Calendar.
  - Gun News Digest, 143
    - Literature, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Gun Owners of America, 144
    - Literature, mass mailings, undated (Box 3)
  - Guns and Ammo Magazine, 145
    - Literature, 1995 (Box 3)
      Boulder
      Articles, excerpts.
  - Himminbjorg Publishing, 146
    - Catalog, undated (Box 3)
      Napa
      Wyrd's Way catalogs.
    - Literature, undated (Box 3)
      National Prison Kindred Alliance materials.
  - The Hornet, 147
    - Mass mailings, undated (Box 3)
      Mokelumne Hill
  - House of Judah, 148
    - Literature, 1971 (Box 3)
      Wetumpka
      Article: "The Truth About the King Alfred Plan (most so-called negroes must die)."
  - HQ (Government Surplus), 149
    - Catalog, 2004 (Box 3)
      St. Paul
      Minnesota
  - Hudson Institute, 150
    - Literature, 2003 (Box 3)
      Indianapolis
      Newsletter.
      Indiana
  - Human Events Publishing, 151
    - Mass mailings, 2009 (Box 3)
      Newspaper inserts and advertisements.
  - Ichthys Books, Inc., 152
    - Catalog, undated (Box 3)
      Glenwood Springs
  - Independent History and Research, 153
    - Catalog, 2006 (Box 3)
      Coeur d'Alene
  - Indiana Civil Liberties Union, 154
    - Literature, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
      Special report; "Carrying the Torch" issue.
  - Institute for Historical Review, 155
    - Catalogs, 1986-2003 (Box 3)
      Costa Mesa
    - Literature, 1979 (Box 3)
      Torrance
      "The Barnes Trilogy," by Harry Elmer Barnes.]
    - Mass mailings, 1990s (Box 3)
      Newport Beach
  - IRSM 1st of May Group, 156
    - Literature, undated (Box 3)
      Photocopy of "Towards a Citizens' Militia" handbook.
  - ISA, 157
    - Catalog, 2003 (Box 3)
      Kapaa
      "Freedom Privacy Catalog."
      Hawaii
  - John Bircher Society, 158
    - Literature, 1969-1978 (Box 3)
      Grand Chute
      Excerpts of American Opinion "De Libris" columns.
  - The Jubilee, 159
    - Mass mailings, undated (Box 3)
  - Kikewatch Stickers, 160
    - Catalog, 1984 (Box 3)
      San Diego
      Sticker catalog.
  - Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (Alabama), 161
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1980s (Box 3)
      Tuscumbia
      Includes photocopy of program from 1981 Klonvokation, membership application, and subscriber letters.
  - Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (Arkansas), 162
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 3)
      Photocopies of fliers, writings by Thomas Robb, and other literature.
  - Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (Georgia), 163
    - Literature, 1947-1958 (Box 3)
      Original early Klorans, Constitution and Laws from the Association of Georgia Klans.
  - Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (Illinois), 164
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1980s (Box 3)
      Villa Park
      Photocopies of fliers, comics, newspaper articles, catalogs; Newspaper insert, "The Knights of the Ku Klux Klan"
  - Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (Louisiana), 165
    - Literature, mass mailings, correspondence, 1980s-2003 (Box 3)
      Metairie
      Includes photocopy of "Constitution, Laws and Ceremonies," mass mailings, and 1991 postcard to Klanwatch.
  - Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (Virginia), 166
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 3)
      Richmond
      Includes photocopy of the "Courier" for the U.S. Klans.
  - Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (general), 167
    - Literature, 1958-1995 (Box 3)
      Publications/pamphlets, including "Constitution and Laws" (1964), "What is a Klansman?" (1971), "Kloran" (3 versions: 1958, 1975, and 1995); other fliers; copy of Neal Payne deposition in Vietnamese Fisherman's Association vs. Knights of the KKK, 1981.
  - Ku Klux Klan (general), 168
    - Literature, 1980s-1990s (Box 3)
      Photocopied clippings, listserv printouts, other materials and Klan coverage.
  - Lawyers' Second Amendment Society, 169
    - Literature, 1997 (Box 3)
      Encino
      Photocopy of "The Liberty Pole" newsletter.
  - League for Peace with Justice in Palestine, 170
    - Literature, 1975 (Box 3)
      Newspaper advertisement essays by Benjamin H. Freedman: "Why Congress is Crooked or Crazy or Both," and "Crisis Nears Climax: Time to Tell the God's Honest Truth"
  - League of the South, 171
    - Mass mailings, 2006 and undated (Box 3)
  - Liberty Bell Publications, 172
    - Catalogs, 1984-2001 (Box 3)
      Reedy
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 3)
      Includes pamphlets such as "An Open Letter to the Gentiles," "Made in Russia: The Holocaust," BBS-Users Group Listing, other fliers.
  - Liberty Fund Books, 173
    - Catalog, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Liberty Knights of the Ku Klux Klan, 174
    - Literature, 1999 (Box 4)
      Boonville
      Sample newsletter of "Liberty Review."
  - Liberty Library, 175
    - Catalog, undated (Box 4)
  - Liberty Lobby, 176
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 4)
      Photocopied excerpts of Spotlight articles.
    - Mass mailings, 1980s (Box 4)
      Newspaper inserts and subscriber letters, including solicitations for funds following Liberty Lobby's libel judgment in Hunt vs. Liberty Lobby.
    - Research file, 1980s-1990s (Box 4)
      SPLC's research file, including correspondence with informants, and a Spotlight Index, 1983-1984.
  - Liberty Tree, 177
    - Catalog, 2000 (Box 4)
      Oakland
  - Loompanics Unlimited, 178
    - Catalogs, 1995-2003 (Box 4)
      Port Townsend
  - Lord's Covenant Church, 179
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 4)
      Photocopies of clippings, America's Promise literature.
  - McAlvany Intelligence Advisor, 180
    - Literature, 1993-1995 (Box 4)
      Photocopies of newsletters.
  - Media Bypass Magazine, 181
    - Literature, 1995 (Box 4)
      Evansville
      Manual: "Outcome Based Education and Higher Order Thinking Skills," by Jeannie Georges.
  - Men of Liberty and Eternity, 182
    - Literature, undated (Box 4)
      Plantersville
      Pamphlet: "Organic Law of Nature."
  - Middle American Institute, 183
    - Mass mailings, 2001 (Box 4)
      Middle American News materials.
  - Militia of Montana, 184
    - Literature, catalogs, 1996-2001 (Box 4)
      Includes parts 1 and 2 of "Taking Aim," and several Preparedness Catalogs.
  - Mission to Israel, 185
    - Literature, 1997-2000 (Box 4)
      Scottsbluff
      Pamphlets and bound volumes. Titles include "Christian Duty Under Corrupt Government," "Eve: Did She or Didn't She?," Yah's Laws: Are They For Today?," and "The Sacred Names of God."
    - Mass mailings, catalogs, 2001-2004 (Box 4)
  - Missouri Patriots, 186
    - Literature, undated (Box 4)
      Buckner
      Copy of "The Militia Minute."
  - Modern Manna Ministries, 187
    - Literature, 1997 (Box 4)
      Lodi
      Booklet, "Is the Virgin Mary Dead or Alive?"
  - Montana Human Rights Network, 188
    - Mass mailings, undated (Box 4)
      Helena
      Provocateur survey.
  - Mountain Church, 189
    - Mass mailings, 1980s (Box 4)
      Cahoctan
      Press releases, mailings.
  - Mountain Church of Northern Ohio, 190
    - Literature, 1983 (Box 4)
      Photocopy of 33/5 by Robert Miles.
  - Mt. Olive Tape Library, Inc., 191
    - Mass mailings, 1995-1997 and undated (Box 4)
      Mt. Olive
      Mississippi
  - Mystery of the Kingdom Ministry, 192
    - Literature, 1982 (Box 4)
      Wausau
      Booklets 1-7: "How to Get the Most Out of a Sermon," "Ezekiel 38 Could Be in the Past," "Study in Genesis, parts 1-4," "Which Day is Our Sabbath?"
    - Literature, 1982 (Box 4)
      Booklets 8-15: "1st Timothy 2:14," "Studies in Genesis, part 5," "Seed of the Woman Mystery," "Lucifer God's Servant," "How to Study the Bible," "Beginning of the Kingdom, part 6-7," "A Voice Crying in the Wilderness, part 8"
  - Nation of Islam, 193
    - Mass mailings, undated (Box 4)
      Farrakhan/The Final Call inserts, booklists.
  - National Alliance, 194
    - Printouts, 2004-2005 (Box 4)
      Hillsboro
      Internet forum printouts.
    - Literature, 1980s-2000s (Box 4)
      Reports, photocopied clippings, other literature about or by the National Alliance.
    - Mass mailings, catalogs, 1980s-1990s (Box 4)
    - Catalogs, 1980s-1990s (Box 4)
      Arlington
      National Vanguard Books catalogs.
    - Literature, 1993 (Box 4)
      New World Order Comix no. 1: The Saga of White Will
  - National Association for the Advancement of White People, 195
    - Literature, undated (Box 4)
      New Orleans
      Photocopied notes; explanation of principles.
  - National Association to Keep and Bear Arms, 196
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1983-1987 (Box 4)
      "Firearms in America: The Costs and Benefits Associated with the Private Citizen Ownership of Firearms" report; bumper sticker; subscriber mailings.
  - National Christian Research, 197
    - Catalog, mass mailings, 1992 (Box 4)
      Ocala
  - National Citizens Action Network, 198
    - Literature, undated (Box 4)
      Photocopy of "Family Protection Scoreboard" magazine.
  - National Democratic Front, 199
    - Literature, 1985 (Box 4)
      Gaithersburg
      "Program of Democratic Nationalism."
      Maryland
  - National Determination Party, 200
    - Research file, 1986 (Box 4)
      Manchester
      Fliers and research notes on Arnold R. Moltis's new group, NDP.
      New Hampshire
  - National Federal Lands Conference, 201
    - Literature, 1994 (Box 4)
      Bountiful
      "Federal Lands Update" photocopy.
  - National Front, 202
    - Literature, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
      Bryan
      Reprints of articles by Harold Covington.
  - National Gulf War Resource Center, 203
    - Literature, 1997 (Box 5)
      Gulf War Syndrome Self-Help Guide.
  - National Investor, 204
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1990s (Box 5)
      Spooner
      Special reports, other materials from editor Chris Temple.
  - National Party, 205
    - Printouts, 1995 (Box 5)
      "Vanguard" printout.
  - National Rifle Association, 206
    - Mass mailings, undated (Box 5)
      Fairfax
      Second Amendment Rights survey.
  - National Socialist American Workers' Party, 207
    - Literature, 2006 and undated (Box 5)
      Roanoke
      Edition of the National Socialist journal; scrapbook page of Nazi clippings.
  - NSWAP, 208
    - Advertising, undated (Box 5)
      Pacific Palisades
      Flier.
  - National Socialist White People's Party, 209
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1994-1999 (Box 5)
      Resistance Records mailings, suggested readings; and articles.
  - National States Rights Party, 210
    - Literature, 1965 (Box 5)
      Birmingham
      Excerpt of "The Thunderbolt."
    - Mass mailings, undated (Box 5)
      "The Thunderbolt" mailings, solicitations.
  - The Nationalist Movement, 211
    - Mass mailings, 1988 (Box 5)
      Cumming
  - Nationalist Socialist Vanguard, 212
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 5)
      Dalles
      Correspondence from Rick Cooper re: NSV Report.
  - Nehemiah Township, 213
    - Literature, 1982 (Box 5)
      Photocopy of Nehemiah Town Charter and Common Law Contract.
  - New Beginnings, 214
    - Catalog, 1995 (Box 5)
      Booklist.
  - New Century Foundation, 215
    - Mass mailings, 1995-2007 (Box 5)
      Oakton
      American Renaissance mailings, inserts.
    - Literature, 2002-2006 (Box 5)
      American Renaissance conference literature.
    - Literature, 1997-2002 (Box 5)
      American Renaissance photocopies, printouts.
  - New Christian Crusade Church, 216
    - Catalog, 2002-2003 (Box 5)
      Sons of Liberty Books catalog.
  - New Covenant Bible Church, 217
    - Literature, undated (Box 5)
      Port Orchard
      "Bible Resource Guide" pamphlet.
  - New Oxford Review, 218
    - Mass mailings, 2004 (Box 5)
      Berkeley
      Advertisement photocopy printed in the Washington Times.
  - Nitro-Pak Preparedness Center, 219
    - Catalog, 1999 (Box 5)
      Heber
      Y2K Survival Catalog.
  - Noontide Press, 220
    - Mass mailings, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
    - Catalogs, 1990-2006 (Box 5)
    - Literature, undated (Box 5)
      Photocopy of "The Road Back," a guide for guerilla war/rebellion.
  - Nordic Heritage and History Club, 221
    - Literature, 1992 and undated (Box 5)
      Photocopies of fliers and articles.
  - Northern Voice Bookstore, 222
    - Catalog, 2004 (Box 5)
      Wildwood
  - Northpoint Tactical Teams, 223
    - Literature, 1988-1990s (Box 5)
      Topton
      Copies of "Pardon Me, But," "Flying Colors," "On Target," and "Desert Shield and the New World Order."
  - NSDAP/AO, 224
    - Mass mailings, catalogs, 1980s-1990s (Box 5)
      Lincoln
      Fliers, subscriptions, solicitations, advertisements.
  - Odin Saves Ministry, 225
    - Literature, 1998 (Box 5)
      Champaign
      Fax from Odin Saves: essays, articles by H.D. Draconi.
  - Operation Freedom, 226
    - Mass mailings, 1994-2000 (Box 5)
      Maitland
      Order forms, mailings, etc. from Charles and Ruth Ann Spross.
  - Oregon Observer, 227
    - Literature, 1997 (Box 5)
      Vol. 3, no. 15 excerpt.
  - Paladin Press, 228
    - Catalogs, 1990s (Box 5)
      Also includes press coverage printouts of Paladin Press.
  - Palladium Press, 229
    - Mass mailings, 1990s (Box 5)
      Promotional materials for the Second Amendment Primer.
  - Paper-House Publications, 230
    - Literature, undated (Box 5)
      "Citizens Rule Book" photocopy.
  - Patriot Freedom Press, 231
    - Catalog, 1990s (Box 5)
  - Pennsylvania Bucktail Militia, 232
    - Literature, 1997 (Box 5)
      Ulysses
      Allegheny Mountain Division newsletter photocopy.
  - People's Advocate, Inc., 233
    - Mass mailings, 1996 (Box 5)
      Petition for an Official English Language Amendment to the U.S. Constitution.
  - "The People's Informer", 234
    - Mass mailings, 1998 (Box 5)
      Cherryfield
      Photocopies of subscriber letters.
      Maine
  - Phoenix Source Distributors, 235
    - Literature, 1993 (Box 5)
      Las Vegas
      "Contact" photocopy.
  - Phoenix Systems, Inc., 236
    - Catalog, 2000 (Box 5)
      Gold Canyon
  - Plymouth Rock Foundation, 237
    - Literature, 1999 (Box 5)
      Marlborough
      Issues of "Letter from Plymouth Rock" newsletters and fliers.
  - Police Against the New World Order, 238
    - Literature, 1996 (Box 5)
      "Operation Vampire Killer 2000" manual, a "American Police/Military Action Plan for Stopping World Government Rule."
  - Polish Freedom Fighters, Inc., 239
    - Literature, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
      Salem
      "S.O.S." publication excerpts.
      Massachusetts
  - Population Communications International, 240
    - Mass mailings, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Populist Party, 241
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 5)
      Allison Park
      "Populist Observer" literature and excerpts.
  - Preparedness Shows, 242
    - Catalog, 1994 (Box 5)
      Expo catalog.
  - The Present Truth, 243
    - Literature, 1994-1998 (Box 5)
      Uniontown
      "Patriot Report" information packets.
    - Literature, catalogs, 1990s (Box 5)
      Pamphlets and catalogs. Titles include "The Present Truth for Israel," "Women and the Militia," "Will 'New World Order' Create Disasters?," and "The Word is Out!"
  - Private Intelligence Network, 244
    - Catalog, 1995 and undated (Box 5)
      Easley
      Includes a faxed excerpted copy of "P.I.N. Newsletter"
      South Carolina
  - Proclaim Liberty Ministry, 245
    - Catalogs, 1990s (Box 5)
      Adrian
  - Punxsutawney Patriots, 246
    - Literature, 1996 (Box 5)
      Punxsutawney
      Photocopies of "Pennsylvania Knightrider."
  - Quartermaster, 247
    - Catalogs, 2004 (Box 5)
      Cerritos
  - Race Traitor, 248
    - Catalog, 2001 (Box 5)
      Cambridge
      New Abolitionist Books website printout.
  - Radio Liberty, 249
    - Catalogs, 2004 (Box 5)
      Soquel
  - Reform Party of California, 250
    - Literature, 1999 (Box 5)
      Covina
      Local chapter newsletter.
  - Resurrection News and Fax Network, 251
    - Literature, undated (Box 5)
      Cornville
      "Firearms Control: No Quarter" article.
  - Rockford Institute, 252
    - Mass mailings, 2000s (Box 5)
      Rockford
      "Chronicles" magazine mailings/solicitations.
  - Rocky Mountain Resistance, 253
    - Literature, 1994 (Box 5)
      Photocopy of "The Denver Ghost" newsletter.
  - Sacred Truth Ministries, 254
    - Literature, 1994 (Box 6)
      Mountain City
      "The Liberty Document."
  - Safe-Trek Outfitters, 255
    - Catalog, 1999 (Box 6)
      Bozeman
      Y2K Meltdown?
  - Samisdat Publishers, 256
    - Catalogs, undated (Box 6)
      Canada
      Toronto (Ont.)
  - Scott-Townsend Publishers, 257
    - Mass mailings, 2001-2002 (Box 6)
      Fliers from "Mankind Quarterly" and "Journal of Social, Political, Economic Studies."
  - Scriptures for America, 258
    - Catalogs, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
      LaPorte
    - Literature, 1998 and undated (Box 6)
      Includes titles "Communion and its Potential Blessings, Curses, and Need," a camp songbook, and "Death Penalty for Homosexuals is Prescribed in the Bible," written by Pastor Peter John Peters.
  - Searchlight Magazine, 259
    - Literature, 2008 (Box 6)
      Special supplement to Searchlight UK: "Searchlight Extra" about Obama.
      England
  - Shiloh Publishing, 260
    - Literature, 1990 and undated (Box 6)
      "Prophetic Nouns" and "Shiloh Separatist" publication, by Elliott Germain.
  - Shomer-Tec, 261
    - Catalog, 2004 (Box 6)
      Bellingham
  - The Social Contract Press, 262
    - Literature, catalogs, mass mailings, 2004 (Box 6)
      Petoskey
      Includes pamphlets "Commons Sense on Mass Immigration" and "The Ethics of Immigration Policy." Published by John Tanton.
  - Social Nationalist Aryan Peoples Party, 263
    - Literature, 1982 and undated (Box 6)
      Post Falls
      "Territorial Imperative" literature by Keith D. Gilbert.
  - Sons of Confederate Veterans, 264
    - Literature, 2002 (Box 6)
      Memphis
      Reunion program.
    - Literature, 2003 (Box 6)
      Photocopy of "Confederate Veteran."
    - Literature, 2002 (Box 6)
      "Guide to Confederate Issues in Kentucky" booklet.
  - Southern League, 265
    - Literature, 1990s (Box 6)
      Tuscaloosa
      Photocopies, clippings, and promotional pamphlets.
  - Southern National Party, 266
    - Literature, undated (Box 6)
      Essay: "White Victory in Memphis and How It Was Done!: Racism, Publicity, and Organization, the Key to Victory."
  - Southwest Radio Church Ministries, 267
    - Literature, 2002 (Box 6)
      Bethany
      Issue of "Prophetic Observer," Vol. 9 no. 1.
  - Sovereignty, 268
    - Literature, mass mailings, 1991 (Box 6)
      Freeport
      Recruitment literature, fliers, etc. opposing high taxes.
  - Special Forces Underground, 269
    - Literature, 1995 (Box 6)
      Photocopies and printouts of "The Resister."
  - The Sportsman's Guide, 270
    - Catalog, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Sprinkle Publications, 271
    - Literature, 1996-1998 (Box 6)
      Harrisonburg
      "Great Revival in the Southern Armies" conference materials.
    - Mass mailings, catalogs, 2000 (Box 6)
  - S.S. Action Group, 272
    - Literature, 1990 and undated (Box 6)
      Drayton Plains
      "Aryans Awake!" publications.
  - Survival Press, 273
    - Catalog, 1999 (Box 6)
      Y2K catalog.
  - Survival Tactics Seminar, 274
    - Literature, 1980s (Box 6)
      Photocopy of a "Survival Tactics Seminar" manual; presumably related to Constitutional Township of Tigerton Dells.
  - Technocracy, Inc., 275
    - Literature, 1996 and undated (Box 6)
      Savannah
      Information briefs.
  - Temple Baptist College, 276
    - Literature, 1996 (Box 6)
      Photocopy of "College Coronet" newsletter.
  - The Tennessean, 277
    - Literature, 1980 (Box 6)
      Nashville
      "New Klan" special report.
  - Texas Patriot Network, 278
    - Literature, 1990 (Box 6)
      Austin
      Copy of a bulletin.
  - Trans-Atlantic Publishing Co., 279
    - Literature, 1995 (Box 6)
      Pavas
      Photocopied literature re: tax havens.
      Costa Rica
  - The Truth At Last, 280
    - Mass mailings, 1990s (Box 6)
      Newspaper inserts and solicitations.
    - Literature, 1980s-1990s (Box 6)
      Pamphlets and articles, including several Truth Tracts.
    - Literature, 1980s-1990s (Box 6)
      Special news reports, sample copies, commemorative editions.
    - Research file, 1980s-2000s (Box 6)
      Correspondence, clippings, and other materials collected by SPLC to monitor Truth At Last newspaper.
  - Truth in History Publications, 281
    - Literature, 2000 (Box 6)
      Springdale
      Pamphlets by Charles A. Jennings, including "Our Southern Heritage: The Confederate Battle Flag," "America's Cultural War: Biblical Christianity and Caucasian Culture," and "The Need of the Angle Israel Truth."
  - Turtle Cove Books, 282
    - Catalogs, 2000 (Box 6)
      Sirius Times catalog.
  - UFO Magazine, 283
    - Literature, 1992 (Box 6)
      Faxed copy of Conspiracies, Part II.
  - Ultramonotane Assoc./Fidelity Press, 284
    - Mass mailings, undated (Box 6)
      South Bend
      "Culture Wars" mailings.
  - Uncommon Media, 285
    - Mass mailings, undated (Box 6)
      "Compass" subscription form.
  - Union Christian Church, 286
    - Literature, 2003 and undated (Box 6)
      Martinsville
      Pamphlets, including "Defending the Faith for Our God, Our Nation, and Our Posterity," "The Separation of Church and State Myth," and a copy of Kingdom Builders Report.
  - United Front Against Facism, 287
    - Mass mailings, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
      Correspondence and news releases.
  - United Klans of America, 288
    - Literature, undated (Box 6)
      Photocopied excerpt of The Fiery Cross.
  - USA Watch, 289
    - Literature, 1995 and undated (Box 6)
      Photocopies of issues.
  - Vanguard News Network, 290
    - Literature, 2001 (Box 6)
      Website printouts.
  - Veritas, 291
    - Literature, 1991 and 2001 (Box 6)
      Louisville
      Newsletters and pamphlets.
  - Virginia Christian Israelites, 292
    - Catalogs, 2000-2003 (Box 6)
      Round Hill
    - Literature, 1990s (Box 6)
      Photocopies of newsletters; clippings with VCI coverage; Directories of Covenant People/Israel Identity; pamphlets and reports, including "The Myth of a Judeo-Christian Tradition," "The Strangest Alias in History," and "Was Jesus Christ a Jew?"
  - Virginia Citizens' Militia, 293
    - Literature, 1997 (Box 6)
      Printout of Southern Ranger newsletter.
  - Virginia Publishing Company, 294
    - Catalogs, 1998-2002 (Box 6)
      Lynchburg
  - Washington Summit Publishers, 295
    - Catalog, 2003 (Box 6)
      Augusta
  - "We Hold These Truths" Magazine, 296
    - Literature, 1995 (Box 6)
      Excerpt.
  - White American Freedom Fighters, 297
    - Literature, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
      Overland
      "The Patriot" photocopies.
  - White Aryan Resistance (W.A.R.), 298
    - Mass mailings, catalogs, undated (Box 6)
      Fallbrook
  - White Camelia Knights of the Ku Klux Klan, 299
    - Literature, 1990 and undated (Box 6)
      Cleveland
  - White House Network, 300
    - Mass mailings, 1997 (Box 6)
      Harrisburg
  - White Patriot Party, 301
    - Mass mailings, 1980s (Box 6)
  - White Sounds, 302
    - Catalogs, 1997 and undated (Box 6)
      Greensboro